[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: This series is created solely for entertainment purposes.
All individuals, behaviors, places, and events depicted are entirely fictional,
with no intention to represent or reference any organizations, departments, occupations, or individuals]
What did you feel
when you were close to her?
I wanted to stop,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't stop myself.
I know your body is rejecting this...
I'll make you want to hug me.
I was in a car accident several years ago.
My doctor said the accident made me
reject physical contact.
What did you feel
when you were close to her?
I wanted to stop,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't stop myself.
This is your life.
Are you going to let guilt stop you from being happy?
If someone who saved me isn't happy,
then how could I be happy?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I have a girlfriend.
[Third Person]
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫
I had been dating my girlfriend for a long time
until an accident happened four years ago.
I lost my memories.
I forgot everything,
including my girlfriend.
She always took care of me,
but my memories never returned.
I can't remember the love I had for her,
and we always argued.
I actually asked to break up,
but her parents pressured me.
So I had to stay with her.
It sounds like an excuse,
but it's the truth.
Things are complicated.
It feels like it's over, but it isn't.
And I don't know when it will actually end.
So you want to stop what happens between us?
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to wrong you and her any further.
I don't want you to be in this terrible relationship.
Someone sweet like you deserves good love.
That doesn't come from you.
I'm sorry...
I'm not in a state to give anyone good love.
So what should we do now?
Should we end it here
and never meet again?
It's up to you.
Then, do you still want to be friends?
Of course I do.
But do you...
want to be friends with someone like me?
What does
"someone like you" mean?
A worthless person
who is unemployed
and never felt like they fit in anywhere.
It's like wearing a bra that's the wrong size all the time?
Sometimes it feels empty,
but sometimes it's uncomfortable.
Where are you going?
Sun, what are you doing?
If you can't pick the right bra, then let me help you.
You have to find the right size.
Explore what you can do.
I don't think
you're worthless.
You were just in the wrong place.
You have to choose a bra that suits your breast shape.
If you know what your strong suit is,
you'll know where you should be.
Lastly... try it out first.
If you feel uncomfortable,
it's okay to run away.
If the bra really is bad,
maybe...
it's better to discard it.
Mm.
I understand now.
I don't know
when I'll find a bra that fits.
But your necklace
never felt uncomfortable.
I really want to be your friend.
Because you pity someone who can't choose her own bra?
No.
It's because you were willing to listen
to what I was saying.
Even though you didn't have to do that.
You make the person you're with feel seen
and acknowledged.
That's the reason
I want to be your friend.
Will you run tomorrow?
I don't know.
I don't want to promise anything.
How about... the day after tomorrow?
I don't know.
It depends if I have work or not.
Okay.
I'll get going now.
Um, Chris?
Can I have your phone?
Here.
If you want to know if I'm running tomorrow,
you can call me.
Okay.
Your "okay" this time
sounds much more cheerful than earlier.
Next time, if you want something, just tell me.
We're friends now.
We can talk about anything.
Do you understand, friend?
Yes, friend.
[Third Person Bar - Bistro]
Nadear,
why did we co-own this restaurant?
You've asked me before, haven't you?
Are you annoyed
that you've had to answer the same question for years?
I'm glad you care, actually.
It makes me feel hopeful.
We opened this restaurant together
because
you've wanted to have your own business since you were a student.
After we graduated,
Nan asked if we wanted to open a restaurant,
so the three of us decided to invest together.
Were the three of us rich?
We borrowed money from our parents to invest.
It was very risky,
but it worked out.
We already paid our parents back in full.
Before you got hurt,
our restaurant was very profitable.
Does that mean it's not as profitable now?
Why?
Is there a problem?
Just the usual problems, Chris.
The economy is bad,
so people don't eat out as much.
But I've seen that we have a lot of customers every day.
You weren't here when we had no customers.
Alright,
then I'll come to our restaurant every day.
You don't have to do that.
You're still recovering,
so I don't want you to be stressed.
But I want to help...
I got this,
but I want to focus on work for now.
Let's talk later, alright, Chris?
Nan,
- Hm? - can I talk to you about our restaurant?
What do you want to know?
I can't remember anything,
so can you start from the beginning?
Whoa, that was years ago.
Why do you want to know now?
Of course I want to know.
Just tell me.
It started when we went to a party together.
I... was Nadear's senior buddy.
Mm, I know that.
I told her...
I want to open my own restaurant.
You and Nadear were interested, so we started it together.
It was going to fail at first, because...
we couldn't find a good spot at a reasonable price.
Until you told me to rent this place.
I didn't know that.
Nadear never told me about this.
You told me
your friend recommended this spot.
Which friend?
I don't know. Ask your girlfriend. Maybe she knows.
Can I talk to her in private?
Of course.
Can you stop asking others about our restaurant?
It doesn't sit well with me.
It looks like you don't know anything about our restaurant.
Well, I don't know anything because you never have time to tell me anything.
If I'm free,
I'll gladly tell you about it.
Why wouldn't I want you to know more about our restaurant?
I'm busy,
and you're not well.
I want you to gradually remember everything,
or maybe wait for me to tell you,
instead of learning things by asking other people.
Then does that mean if I can't remember,
I don't have the right to know anything about our restaurant?
I don't want to be like this forever.
I want to be normal.
I want to know what I did in the past.
I want to know everything.
I don't want to keep trying to remember things, but nothing comes to mind.
Don't you get it?
Okay, Chris,
from now on,
I'll answer all of your questions.
Then... which one of my friends told us to rent this place?
Chris suddenly became interested in our restaurant.
She asked me so many questions.
Doesn't that mean Chris is interested in you?
No.
It means Chris is trying to be independent.
She doesn't want to depend on me.
What did you make of that?
She's practically trying to break up with me.
You're overthinking it.
Chris is perfectly fine.
She thought I cared about her again,
but I really don't feel anything towards her anymore.
I'm just trying to live my life.
Is this what you call giving her false hope?
How can you stop someone from hoping?
Follow your heart.
If you don't feel anything,
then show her that you don't.
Nadear will definitely understand.
I don't want to upset her.
Then are you upset
that you didn't get to live the way you wanted?
If you still hold each other back,
no one is going to be happy.
Right?
As a doctor,
what do you think?
It's a good sign.
She's trying to get into your world.
Really?
Yes.
If there's something off,
you'll be the first to know.
Can you stop asking others about our restaurant?
Then... which one of my friends told us to rent this place?
I forgot.
If I can remember, I'll tell you.
Let's discuss what you want to know later.
You make the person you're with feel seen
and acknowledged.
That's the reason
I want to be your friend.
Chris, you have to understand.
I have important things to deal with right now.
I just saw your call.
If you're asking me to go running,
I'll have to decline.
Sun...
can I come to your room?
Tell me why you wanted to talk to me this early.
I... want to talk to you.
Alright,
but let's not stand while we talk.
When it's early like this...
I don't want to deal with gravity yet.
You can get straight to the point.
I want to ask you something.
Make some eye contact when you talk, friend.
So,
what would you like to talk about?
[Third Person]
So, what would you like to talk about?
Why don't you say anything?
Or...
you want to do something else first?
I want to do something else first.
Ooh!
Gay panic, huh?
Tease me however you want.
Alright, I'm ready.
Sun... don't do this.
I'm trying to hold myself back.
Then when will you stop holding back?
Sun...
I'll stop.
So, what do you want to talk about?
Go ahead.
Well...
What would you do
if you had a friend
who wouldn't discuss anything important in your life
because she always had other important things to do?
Your girlfriend?
If she won't discuss it with you,
you'll have to make her realize
you're important.
[Third Person Bar - Bistro]
If she won't discuss it with you,
you'll have to get her attention.
How?
I'll show you.
You'll play someone who's strong-willed.
Easy.
I'm very strong-willed.
You won't sway me.
See? I don't feel anything.
Hey,
that's no fun.
Sun!
Sun.
Are you alright?
Success!
Oh, so you tricked me?
Would I even get your attention otherwise?
Why don't you do what your friend wants you to do?
Maybe she'll drop everything
and take an interest in you.
Leave it to me.
What happened?
I wanted to ask you that too.
Chris suddenly swooped in to serve that dish.
Chris,
what are you doing?
I'm serving food.
I'm serious.
Isn't this our restaurant?
I have to work, don't I?
One moment, please.
What would you like?
What's gotten into her?
She's enthusiastic.
Has she recovered?
That's why you let her work, right?
One Wagyu green curry and soda set.
Can we talk?
Do I have to do something you don't like
before you'll have time to talk to me?
Are you going to stop me again?
I'm not,
but we already have a lot of waiters.
If you want to work,
go back to what you were doing.
What I was doing?
Behind-the-scenes stuff, marketing.
Thinking of new ways to attract customers.
If you can do it,
you can come back to work as before.
Let's go.
- The movie was fun, yeah? - Mm.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Drive home safe.
Chris!
When did you get here?
I arrived just as you came down with that woman.
Why didn't you greet me then?
That's Oil,
my best friend.
"Friend"?
Mm, friend.
Just like you.
Did you come to see me about something?
Congratulations, you got back to work.
It's because of you.
Without you, I'd probably be living without a goal.
You gave me a goal in life, too.
One second.
I bought you a sandwich.
Thanks.
In case you're hungry tonight.
There's something in your hair.
Go rest up. Good night.
Bye.
- See you. - See you.
Look.
Isn't she extra?
She still came back to get me this sandwich after she left.
She's probably worried I might not have anything to eat
because we have a date tomorrow morning.
Date?
Mm.
A date to relieve some stress.
Would you like to join us?
Oil won't mind.
It's okay, you guys go ahead.
I changed my mind.
May I join you?
[Third Person]
- Here are my papers. - Thank you.
- I'll be in your care. - One moment, please.
Oh, Sun.
This is Oil.
She's a doctor.
We studied together,
and she's also a shareholder in my clinic.
Work is tough right now,
so Oil invited me to take a flower arrangement class.
She told me it helps relieve stress.
I'm Chris.
Can I join you today?
You don't need my permission.
Anyone can take the class.
Just sign up there.
Shall we...
go look at the flowers inside?
Mm.
Go ahead, I'll sign up first.
Chris can take care of herself,
right?
Let's go.
Alright, everyone,
before we start arranging the flowers,
I want you to picture
who you want to give these flowers to
and why.
This way, the flowers can truly fulfill their purpose.
Sun,
I'll...
arrange these flowers for you.
Fine,
but if it's not beautiful, I don't want it.
I'll shove it into your hands anyway.
First, let's prepare the roses.
Alright, everyone, look here.
Pluck off any leaves
that are below where we'll tie them together.
Take them all off to clear it up.
Be careful of the thorns, too.
Follow my steps.
You can cut off the thorns.
Hey, need help?
Here, I'll help.
Be careful of the thorns.
You too.
Ow!
Um...
I'll go treat it first.
Can I help?
Are you very close to Oil?
Does it look that way?
Yes...
We're close.
We studied together,
worked together,
went through good and bad things together.
Without her,
I wouldn't be here learning about flower arrangement.
She seems to be a very important person for you.
I admit
that she's important to me.
Am I intruding on your date with someone important?
Are you jealous?
How can a friend be jealous of this?
I just want to tell you that
if we hadn't met,
I wouldn't be taking a flower arrangement class here either.
Let's go back inside.
Well done, everyone.
But don't forget
to let the flowers you worked hard to arrange today
fulfill their purpose.
This is for you.
I thought you were joking.
Well, you know I'm serious.
So, I'll go to the clinic after this.
Wanna grab something to eat?
I'm sorry.
Maybe next time. I have to go.
Can you take this to the clinic for me?
I'll see you later.
Mm.
Chris!
Wait for me!
Sun, don't cross the road yet!
What is it?!
I haven't let my flowers fulfill their purpose yet.
Me too.
I thought I wouldn't be able to give it to you.
You have to.
It's your goal, isn't it?
So...
why are you giving me your flowers?
To celebrate our meeting.
What about you?
To say I'm glad I got to see you again.
Wow.
I was planning to treat you to our first meal together,
but you only wanted Pad Thai. That's it?
Well, I like it.
You do, too.
Mm, that's true.
How did you know that?
- Your water. - Thank you.
What would you like today?
Two Pad Thais and one fried mussel pancake, no bean sprouts, please.
Alright.
Thank you.
Hey...
I'm sorry.
I... ordered for you without asking first.
No need to.
You ordered correctly.
How did you know
that I don't like bean sprouts?
I didn't.
When I had to order the food, I just said it without thinking.
Why are you smiling?
I'm happy.
It's like...
god is finally on my side.
Thank you.
Hey, kids!
What are you doing? Fighting again, huh?!
Oh!
Come on!
Go home!
Hey...
are the flowers okay?!
It's okay, Chris.
It's okay.
Will it get bruised?
It's still pretty.
Even if the flowers aren't in a bouquet,
they're still pretty.
This is it.
This is something new my restaurant needs.
Thank you so much, Sun.
Where've you been today, Chris?
Nice flowers.
Who gave them to you?
It's mine.
I took a flower arranging class.
With who?
My friend.
Since when did you have a friend?
We met when I was out running.
You haven't told me this before.
Introduce me to them.
I want to get to know your friend, too.
Okay...
Where are you taking it?
You're the same as always, huh?
The same...?
You like roses.
When you were younger,
you loved the rose I gave you so much.
You don't remember, do you?
But I'm glad
that you chose these roses.
It means deep down...
you haven't forgotten me yet.
You haven't forgotten about us.
Just a bit longer...
I miss the you from back then.
I want the Chris I know back.
Here.
Did you buy these to give to people?
No,
they're offerings for Buddha.
Then no thanks. I don't want to take one meant for Buddha.
This one isn't an offering.
I want to give it to you.
Wait!
When are you going to stop flirting with someone who already has a girlfriend?
They already broke up.
That's what everyone who wants someone who's taken says.
If she can't make their relationship public,
don't play with her.
I didn't start it.
You saw how she felt about me, right?
It doesn't matter how much she likes you.
As long as she hasn't broken up with her girlfriend
and told you that you're just a friend,
doesn't that mean she doesn't choose you?
[Third Person]
I want to add edible flowers to our dishes.
So that we have something new
that's pretty,
appetizing,
and photogenic.
I think it could attract more customers.
What do you think?
I agree.
It's pretty interesting.
Thanks, Nadear.
Thanks, Nan.
Something new? Flowers? Really?
No other restaurants do this, yeah?
How did you agree?
Chris is a shareholder as well.
I want Chris to do this.
You say it's good, but is it good
for our business?
Or is it for the relationship between you two?
Can you stop asking about my personal life?
Be more rational, Nadear.
Do you really think
these edible flowers
won't be a waste of our budget?
I insist on letting Chris do it.
Even if it's bad,
wasteful,
not worthwhile,
or a loss for us.
Is that really okay?
What are you thinking?
Stop fighting.
I'll make this flower dish worthwhile
and profitable.
I don't think your idea is bad.
I just said that to get Nan to let you do it.
I didn't want to upset you.
When will you understand
that I don't want you to protect me like this?
I want sincerity.
When will you stop treating me like someone about to die?
You wouldn't know
how much pain I was in
when you were dying.
Chris!
I don't want to see you in pain
or see you sad anymore,
because I love you!
Am I wrong for that?
I'm the one who loves you more.
Am I that wrong?
I'm sorry...
You don't want me to feel sad
because my idea was that terrible?
Didn't you say you wanted to be my friend?
Why are you avoiding me?
I can't bring myself to see you.
I'm an awful person.
There's no place where I fit.
If it doesn't fit, then why don't you throw it away?
Because it used to be amazing, I guess?
That's why I can't discard it...
What?
Then what about the flowers in the dish?
It'd be better if I didn't do anything.
Let's go.
Where?
Somewhere to make you stop thinking you're awful.
♫The umbrella we once used to share♫
♫Two bodies leaning close beneath the rain♫
♫I never felt cold in your warmth♫
♫Because you were there every time♫
Do I hold the light here?
Yes.
See? It came out beautifully.
But...
If we do this, won't it be a loss?
You can make it profitable.
Trust me.
Give it a try,
so you'll know
you're not as awful as you think.
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
Whoa,
The food cost for this flower dish is thirty percent.
Then that means...
we have around seventy percent profit.
I think it could work after we subtract other expenses.
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
See? You're not awful.
I'm good in theory.
What if people don't buy it?
Well...
it's going to be sad.
But isn't it sadder
if you didn't do what you love,
didn't follow your heart?
Would life have any meaning that way?
Thank you so much, Sun.
Can I hug you?
You can drop me off here.
I can take you home.
It's okay.
I'll get there myself.
You helped a lot already.
It's my pleasure.
If your car isn't fixed yet,
you can call me.
Your chauffeur is on standby.
Thank you so much, Sun.
I stopped feeling like an awful person because of you.
You're a "talented one" now, aren't you?
Good job.
Thank you, really.
Are you kissing as thanks?
Mm...
Friends don't kiss, do they?
I'll go now.
We were never friends, Chris...
I kissed you,
because I don't want to be just friends.
Even though I can't recall anything,
my heart still flutters
every time I see that smile.
I won't let anyone come between us.
Can you give me three months?
Three months to go back to how it used to be.
I don't want to keep living like this anymore, Nadear.
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫